Guide to the Coca Crystal Video Recordings and Papers MSS.468
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. The Coca Crystal Show: If I Can't Dance, You Can Keep Your Revolution, 1977-1995
  - Dreams, December 15, 1982; cuid29747 (Box 10, U-matic 468_136)
  - Tristan Jones, Author of "A Steady Trade", December 22, 1982; cuid29748 (Box 10, U-matic 468_137)
  - The Regulars (Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, Rebecca, Bud Bogart), January 5, 1983; cuid29749 (Box 10, U-matic 468_138)
  - Tristan Jones, Author of "A Steady Trade", January 5, 1983; cuid29750 (Box 10, U-matic 468_139)
  - Anarchy in America, January 12, 1982; cuid29751 (Box 11, U-matic 468_140)
  - Henry Schwanzchild (ACLU), Capital Punishment Project, Eric Silvey (Dancer), January 19, 1983; cuid29752 (Box 11, U-matic 468_141)
    This episode also features Vincent Titus, Margaret Titus, Lannes Kenfield, and Mike Chance.
  - Michelle Shocked, January 30, 1983; cuid29753 (Box 11, U-matic 468_142)
  - The Red Squad - Michael Warren Powell, Steven Fischler, Joel Sucher, February 2, 1983; cuid29754 (Box 11, U-matic 468_143)
  - Ganesh Babe and Friends, February 9, 1983; cuid29755 (Box 11, U-matic 468_144)
  - Keep Your Dopey Revolution, February 23, 1983; cuid29756 (Box 11, U-matic 468_145)
  - Michio Kaku, March 2, 1983; cuid29757 (Box 11, U-matic 468_146)
  - Panel on Gay Rights, March 9, 1983; cuid29758 (Box 11, U-matic 468_147)
    This episode also features Lawrence Cherniak, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfields, Nancy Borman, Joe Shulman, David Klein, and Beanie the Singing Dog.
  - Grace Seid, I Ching Instructor, March 23, 1983; cuid29759 (Box 11, U-matic 468_148)
    This episode also features Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, Joe Shulman, Bud Bogart, and Lawrence Cherniak.
  - Carol De Saram - Capra Beetle, N.J. Normal, March 30, 1983; cuid29760 (Box 11, U-matic 468_149)
  - Tuli Kupferberg, Lawrence Cherniak, April 6, 1983; cuid29761 (Box 11, U-matic 468_150)
    This episode also features Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, Joe Shulman, and Bud Bogart.
  - Gerard Malanga, Nat Finkelstein, April 13, 1983; cuid29762 (Box 11, U-matic 468_151)
    This episode also features Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Jim Buckley, Joe Schulman, Nancy Borman, and Bud Bogart.
  - Lawrence Cherniak, April 20, 1983; cuid29605 (Box 35, U-matic 468_152)
    This episode also features Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, and Joe Schulman.
  - Pete Mahoney (VVAW), Dana Beal (Yippies), May 4, 1983; cuid29998 (Box 29, U-matic 468_408)
  - Lisa Knower, Jared, C.I.S.P.E.S., Greens, May 11, 1983; cuid29999 (Box 29, U-matic 468_409)
  - Improv-o-rama, May 18, 1983; cuid30000 (Box 29, U-matic 468_410)
  - Caldwell Taylor, Ambassador from Grenada, May 25, 1983; cuid30001 (Box 29, U-matic 468_411)
  - Special Olympics, June 1, 1983; cuid30002 (Box 29, U-matic 468_412, Box 30, U-matic 468_427)
  - Stephen Holt, June 8, 1983; cuid30003 (Box 29, U-matic 468_413)
    This also features an announcement by Jim Buckley, Kaptioned Kartoon Korner with Lannes Kenfield, Cat Food Commercial with voiceover by Jim Buckley, News with Nancy Borman and Coca Crystal, answering phones with Cocacita, Dream Man with Joe Schulman, and Sinsemilla Street with Bud Bogart.
  - Jerry Lasso, Wallflower Order, June 15, 1983; cuid30004 (Box 30, U-matic 468_414)
    Duration: 60 Minutes.
  - First Show, October 5, 1983; cuid30005 (Box 30, U-matic 468_415)
  - Jill Diamond, October 12, 1983; cuid30006 (Box 30, U-matic 468_416, Box 32, Vhs 468_467)
    This episode also features a poem by Vincent Titus, Kaptioned Kartoon Korner with Lannes Kenfield, Dream Man with Joe Schulman, News from Albania with Nancy Borman, Phone calls with Coca, and Sinsemilla Street with Bud Bogart.
    Duration: 60 minutes.
  - The Harvest, October 19, 1983; cuid30007 (Box 30, U-matic 468_417)
    This episode also features an announcement by Jim Buckley, a poem by Vincent Titus, Cartoon Corner with Lannes Kenfield, The Dream Man with Joe Schulman, News with Nancy Borman and Coca Crystal, Phones with Coca, and Sinsemilla Street with Bud Bogart.
  - Sefton Rodney, Pete Mastrangelo, Anti-ROTC, October 26, 1983; cuid29763 (Box 11, U-matic 468_153)
  - Wildman, Grenada Song by Tuli Kupferberg, November 2, 1983; cuid29764 (Box 12, U-matic 468_154)
  - Joe Schulman, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Grenada's ambassador to the U.N. Caldwell Taylor, November 9, 1983; cuid29765 (Box 12, U-matic 468_155)
  - Barbara George, November 15, 1983; cuid29766 (Box 12, U-matic 468_156)
  - Michio Kaku, December 14, 1983; cuid29767 (Box 12, U-matic 468_157)
  - The Lonely Revolution, December 28, 1983; cuid29768 (Box 12, U-matic 468_158)
  - Merle Hoffman, "Choices", January 11, 1984; cuid29769 (Box 12, U-matic 468_159)
    This episode also features Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, Joe Schulman, and Bud Bogart.
  - John Douglas, John Glover, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Joe Schulman, Bud Bogart, January 18, 1984; cuid29770 (Box 12, U-matic 468_160)
  - Stephen Holt and the Boys, February 1, 1984; cuid29771 (Box 12, U-matic 468_161)
    This episode also features Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, Joe Schulman, and Cooking with Maureen Ivice and Coca Crystal.
  - Alan Armstrong, February 15, 1984; cuid29606 (Box 35, U-matic 468_162)
  - Memorial to Nick Yanni, February 22, 1984; cuid29772 (Box 12, U-matic 468_163)
  - Cooking Special: Tempeh Nite with Susan Firing and Maureen Ivice, March 14, 1984; cuid29607 (Box 35, U-matic 468_164, Box 29, Vhs 468_394)
    cuid29607B duration: 30 minutes
  - Rebecca Ann Chanee, March 28, 1984; cuid29773 (Box 12, U-matic 468_165)
    This episode also features Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, Joe Schulman, and fabulous phone-ins.
  - "Burn Out" Master, April 3, 1984; cuid29608 (Box 35, U-matic 468_166)
  - Reverend Kirkpatrick, Terri Sosa, Jill Seiden, Phone Call with Steve Silos, April 4, 1984; cuid29774 (Box 12, U-matic 468_167)
    This episode also features Jim Buckley, Vincent Titus, Lannes Kenfield, and Joe Schulman.
  - Judith Malina, April 25, 1984; cuid29609 (Box 35, U-matic 468_168)
  - Helen Brungardt, Abbie Hoffman (on phone), May 2, 1984; cuid29991 (Box 29, Vhs 468_395)
  - Rainbow Family, May 8, 1984; cuid30037N (Box 32, Vhs 468_466)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: First 30 minutes has audio, but no video.
  - Joanie Freedom, Garnick Beck, the Rainbow Gathering Picnic, Music by Larry Estridge, Co-Hosted by Gus as the Hulk, May 9, 1984; cuid29775 (Box 13, U-matic 468_169)
  - Alan Armstrong, Craig Silver, May 16, 1984; cuid29776 (Box 13, U-matic 468_170)
  - Teflon, celebrity phone call with Cyndi Lauper, May 23, 1984; cuid29777 (Box 13, U-matic 468_007)
  - A Tribute to Hand-Wash, by Coca Crystal; Folding a Fitted Sheet, starring Lois Chaffee; The Dream Man by Joe Schulman, May 30, 1984; cuid29610 (Box 35, U-matic 468_171)
  - Tuli Kupferberg, Baby Jerry, June 6, 1984; cuid29778 (Box 13, U-matic 468_173)
  - Lannes Kenfield, Nancy Borman, Joe Schulman, September 26, 1984; cuid29992 (Box 29, Vhs 468_396)
  - Paul Ropp, Nat Finkelstein, October 3, 1984; cuid30037M (Box 32, Vhs 468_465)
  - Judy Belushi, Anne Beatts, Deanne Stillman, October 11, 1984; cuid29779 (Box 13, U-matic 468_174, Box 32, Vhs 468_465)
  - Stephen Holt, Maureen Ivice, Vincent Titus, October 17, 1984; cuid29611 (Box 35, U-matic 468_175, Box 29, Vhs 468_397)
  - The Fugs - Tuli Kupferberg, Kramer, Lannes Kenfield, October 24, 1984; cuid29612 (Box 35, U-matic 468_176, Box 29, Vhs 468_398)
    A note on 468_176 case says "Bad Tape, Damaged Tape"
  - Lannes Kenfield, Bud Thomas, Jim Glover, Ivis, Ray Corona, Gus, October 31, 1984; cuid29780 (Box 13, U-matic 468_177)
    Coca Crystal and guests discuss Halloween and Election Day 1984.
  - Michelle Shocked, November 7, 1984; cuid29781 (Box 13, U-matic 468_178, Box 31, U-matic 468_440)
  - Phillip Core, November, 1984; cuid30011 (Box 30, U-matic 468_422)
    Duration: 60 Minutes
  - Unlabeled, November 21, 1984; cuid29615 (Box 35, U-matic 468_468)
  - Olatunji, November 28, 1984; cuid30010 (Box 30, U-matic 468_421)
  - Michelle Shocked, Elliot Teplitz, Headly Gritter, December 12, 1984; cuid29782 (Box 13, U-matic 468_179)
    A note on the videotape also says "Tapes of Vincent [Titus] and Olatunji"
  - John Darling (Last Show of 1984), December, 1984; cuid29837 (Box 17, U-matic 468_236)
  - David Burak, Jim Glover, January 2, 1985; cuid29795 (Box 14, U-matic 468_192, Box 29, Vhs 468_399)
    468_192 duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: Tape needed to be baked, signal improved; low audio at the beginning.
  - Sheldon Cholst, David Peel, January 9, 1985; cuid29993 (Box 29, Vhs 468_399)
  - Terry Noel, February 6, 1985; cuid29796 (Box 14, U-matic 468_193)
  - Jim Mason, February 13, 1985; cuid29783 (Box 13, U-matic 468_180)
  - Georgelle, Writer in the Window, February 27, 1985; cuid29784 (Box 13, U-matic 468_181)
  - Master Show #145, March 6, 1985; cuid29785 (Box 13, U-matic 468_182)
  - Vincent's Memorial, March 13, 1985; cuid29786 (Box 14, U-matic 468_183)
  - John Howell of "The High Times," Bad Altitudes, Film with Gus and the regulars, March 20, 1985; cuid29787 (Box 14, U-matic 468_184)
  - John Wilcox, March 27, 1985; cuid29788 (Box 14, U-matic 468_185)
  - Earl Manning and Bessie, April 17, 1985; cuid29789 (Box 14, U-matic 468_186)
  - No Biz As Usual, April 24, 1985; cuid29790 (Box 14, U-matic 468_187)
  - Cooking Show - Tempeh '85 with Ivice and Susan Firing, May 1, 1985; cuid29792 (Box 14, U-matic 468_189)
  - Terry Noel, Barnaby Rube, May 15, 1985; cuid29793 (Box 14, U-matic 468_190)
  - Carl Dix, Holy War, Jack McCrystal, Plutonium Players, May 22, 1985; cuid29794 (Box 14, U-matic 468_191)
    This episode also features regulars Lannes Kenfield, Marty Brown, Vincent Titus, and Jim Buckley.
  - Homeless Show: Beth Gorrie, Mollie Smollett, May 28, 1985; cuid29995 (Box 29, Vhs 468_401, Box 20, U-matic 468_272)
  - Homeless Show: Beth Gorrie, Mollie Smollett, May 28, 1985; cuid29871 (Box 20, U-matic 468_272)
  - Earl Manning, Holy War, Jack McCrystal, Local 802, May 29, 1985; cuid29791 (Box 14, U-matic 468_188, Box 23, U-matic 468_318)
    468_188 duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: Tape needed to be baked, signal improved. 468_318 duration: 120 minutes.
  - Jock McCrystal, Rick Nestler, Zimmer and Zimmerman, June 5, 1985; cuid29838 (Box 17, U-matic 468_237, Box 23, Vhs 468_318)
    468_237 duration: 60 minutes
  - Season Finale Party Featuring Eddie Brown and Dennis Glover, June 12, 1985; cuid29797 (Box 14, U-matic 468_194)
  - Halloween Special (Master), October 30, 1985; cuid29798 (Box 14, U-matic 468_195)
  - Tuli Kupferberg, the Fuxxons, February 12, 1986; cuid29799 (Box 14, U-matic 468_196)
    This episode also features Lannes Kenfield with "Media Madness."
  - Lannes Kenfield, March 19, 1986; cuid29994 (Box 29, Vhs 468_400)
  - Tuli Kupferberg, Lannes Kenfield, Stephen Holt, Billy Hower, July 9, 1986; cuid29800 (Box 15, U-matic 468_197)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: Tape needed to be baked.
  - Vincent Titus, The Chanterelle Twins, August 20, 1986; cuid29801 (Box 15, U-matic 468_198)
  - New Name Show: 10th Season Premiere, September 24, 1986; cuid29802 (Box 15, U-matic 468_199, Box 29, Vhs 468_403)
  - Halloween Call-In, October 29, 1986; cuid29843 (Box 18, U-matic 468_244, Box 30, U-matic 468_420)
  - Halloween Call-In, October 29, 1986; cuid29803 (Box 15, U-matic 468_200)
  - Thanksgiving with Judith Malina, November 26, 1986; cuid29804 (Box 15, U-matic 468_201)
  - Steve Gruberg, Tuli Kupferberg, December 17, 1986; cuid29805 (Box 15, U-matic 468_202)
    This episode also features music by Mona More and Jim Buckley; also featuring regulars Lannes Kenfield, Stephen Holt, Nancy Borman, and Vincent Titus.
  - Christopher Robbins - "A Fan Speaks Out", January 28, 1987; cuid29806 (Box 15, U-matic 468_203)
  - Bob Fass, Tuli Kupferberg, Mushroom Larry, February 25, 1987; cuid29807 (Box 15, U-matic 468_204)
  - Aruba - Ivice and Stephen Holt, April 22, 1987; cuid29809 (Box 15, U-matic 468_206)
  - Morrison, June 24, 1987; cuid29808 (Box 15, U-matic 468_205)
  - Mushrooms, July 22, 1987; cuid29872 (Box 20, U-matic 468_273)
  - John Diamond, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg and the Fugs, Stephen Holt, Betsy Widhalm, September 2, 1987; cuid29873 (Box 20, U-matic 468_274)
  - Ponderosa Pine Special, September 27, 1987; cuid29875 (Box 20, U-matic 468_276)
  - Tuli's Birthday, Bouncers, September 30, 1987; cuid29876 (Box 20, U-matic 468_277)
  - Abbie Hoffman, Judith Malina, September-October, 1987; cuid29874 (Box 20, U-matic 468_275)
    Labels on the tape itself say "Allan's 18 Comical Situations - Pub" and "Broadcast of '38 (George Pal Puppetoon)"
  - Ivice - Time After Time, Stephen Holt, Everett Quintin, Tulit Steve Taylor, October 28, 1987; cuid29810 (Box 15, U-matic 468_207)
  - Thanksgiving Show: Steve Teller, Keegan and Lloyd, the Oil City Symphony, November 25, 1987; cuid29811 (Box 15, U-matic 468_208)
  - Holiday Special: Steven Holt, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Efrom Allen, December 16, 1987; cuid29812 (Box 15, U-matic 468_209)
  - Susan Rankin, Judith Malina, January 5, 1988; cuid29816 (Box 16, U-matic 468_213)
    This episode also features regulars Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, and Stephen Holt.
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: This tape was baked.
  - Lorenzo La Rock, Cocteau Repertory Theatre, February 3, 1988; cuid29817 (Box 16, U-matic 468_214, Box 29, Vhs 468_402)
    468_214 Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: This tape was baked.
  - Boys Next Door - Ky Hote, February 24, 1988; cuid29818 (Box 16, U-matic 468_215)
  - Sally Kirkland, Lannes Kenfield, Stephen Holt, March 16, 1988; cuid29813 (Box 15, U-matic 468_210)
  - Maria Lions: Reproductive Freedom Week, April 20, 1988; cuid29814 (Box 16, U-matic 468_211)
    Also featuring Lannes Kenfield, Steven Holt, Cooking Spring Foods with Ivy, and Jacaeber Kastor from Psychedelic Solutions.
    Duration: 60 minutes. Preservation note: this tape needed to be baked.
  - Lannes Kenfield hosts, Dave Street, Tuli Kupferberg, Steve Taylor, Stephen Holt, Elise Stone, May 11, 1988; cuid30037D (Box 32, U-matic 468_456)
  - Representatives from the American Indian Community House (Did not appear), Tuli Kupferberg and the Fuxxons, Lynn Oliver, May 18, 1988; cuid29815 (Box 16, U-matic 468_212)
    Duration: 60 minutes. Sound low.
  - Psychedelic Solution with Bob Fass, Jacabar Kastor, June 8, 1988; cuid29819 (Box 16, U-matic 468_216)
    This episode also features regulars Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Steve Taylor, and Stephen Holt.
  - Brian Benson, Holt Interview, Joe Turner Dir., Mecca Dir., June 22, 1988; cuid29613 (Box 36, U-matic 468_217)
  - David Peel, 10% Review, Sara Jenkins, Judith Malina, July 20, 1988; cuid29820 (Box 16, U-matic 468_218)
  - Mushroom Show with Sara Ann Friedman, False Prophets, Jack Wetherau of Tamama, September 28, 1988; cuid29821 (Box 16, U-matic 468_219, Box 29, Vhs 468_404)
  - Halloween Episode: Lannes Kenfield, Stephen Holt, David Blackman, Tuli Kupferberg, October 26, 1988; cuid29822 (Box 16, U-matic 468_220)
  - Cookie, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Stephen Holt, November 23, 1988; cuid29823 (Box 16, U-matic 468_221)
    This episode also features Brett (?), Scott on the Banjo, and Bloolips.
  - Christmas Special: Tribute to Miss Christine, Calls from Frank Zappa and Deputy Dawg, December 21, 1988; cuid29834 (Box 17, U-matic 468_232)
    This episode also features regulars Stephen Holt, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, and Gus Finkelstein.
  - Unlabelled Master, January 24, 1989; cuid29826 (Box 16, U-matic 468_224)
  - Henry - Animal Rights, January 25, 1989; cuid29916 (Box 23, Vhs 468_317)
  - Steve Ben Israel, Celso Loch, Lorenzo La Rock, February 22, 1989; cuid29827 (Box 17, U-matic 468_225, Box 23, Vhs 468_317)
  - AIDS Demo, Cooking, March 22, 1989; cuid29828 (Box 17, U-matic 468_226)
  - Abbie Hoffman Memorial, April 19, 1989; cuid29829 (Box 17, U-matic 468_227, 468_228)
  - Nat Finkelstein, Jeff Nightbyrd, Ponderosa Pine, Robin Byrd, May 21, 1989; cuid29831 (Box 17, U-matic 468_229)
    This episode also features regulars Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, and Steven Holt. It was directed by Christian Roebling.
  - The Fuxxons, October 25, 1989; cuid29832 (Box 17, U-matic 468_230)
  - Junot the Dog, February 7, 1990; cuid29835 (Box 17, U-matic 468_233)
  - Judith Malina, "Jerusalem" by Tuli Kupferberg, March 14, 1990; cuid29844 (Box 18, U-matic 468_245)
  - Yippie Mayhem with Buzzy Linhart, Clayton Preston, Mickey the Pope, David Peel, and Gus, April 11, 1990; cuid29836 (Box 17, U-matic 468_234, 468_235)
    468_234 duration: 60 minutes; 468_235 duration: 60 minutes
  - Deloris Holmes, Leona Zions, May 9, 1990; cuid29877 (Box 20, U-matic 468_278)
    This episode also features regulars Maureen Ivice, Lannes Kenfield, and Tuli Kupferberg.
  - Steve "Wildman" Brill, June 6, 1990; cuid29878 (Box 20, U-matic 468_279)
  - Nancy Cohn, Tuli Kupferberg and the Fuxxons, July 11, 1990; cuid29855 (Box 19, U-matic 468_256)
  - Rev, August 15, 1990; cuid29879 (Box 20, U-matic 468_280)
  - Robin Byrd, September 12, 1990; cuid29880 (Box 21, U-matic 468_281)
  - Bob Fass, Nat Finkelstein, October 10, 1990; cuid29881 (Box 21, U-matic 468_282, Box 23, Vhs 468_319)
    468_319 Duration: 120 minutes
  - Steve Ben Israel, Cliff Roth, November 7, 1990; cuid29882 (Box 21, U-matic 468_283)
  - Pat McGrath, Brian and Paul, Steve Taylor, and Jasmine, January 9, 1991; cuid29883 (Box 21, U-matic 468_284)
    This episode also features regulars Tuli Kupferberg and Lannes Kenfield.
  - Gulf War: Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Brian Benson, February 6, 1991; cuid29614 (Box 36, U-matic 468_405)
  - After the War..., March 6, 1991; cuid29884 (Box 21, U-matic 468_285)
  - Kevin O'Neill, Mark Furstenberg, Brian Benson, Lannes Kenfield, April 3, 1991; cuid29885 (Box 21, U-matic 468_286)
  - Lorian Boyer from Hands Off, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, May 1, 1991; cuid29917 (Box 23, U-matic 468_320)
  - Judith Malina, June 5, 1991; cuid29918 (Box 23, U-matic 468_321)
  - Chris Flash from the Shadow, Kevin O'Neill, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, July 3, 1991; cuid29839 (Box 17, U-matic 468_238)
  - Chris Flash from the Shadow, Brian Benson, Lannes Kenfield, July 17, 1991; cuid29919 (Box 23, U-matic 468_322)
  - David Peel, August 7, 1991; cuid29937 (Box 25, U-matic 468_340)
  - Terry Noel, September 4, 1991; cuid29856 (Box 19, U-matic 468_257)
  - Coca Crystal and Lannes Kenfield, September 4, 1991; cuid29920 (Box 23, U-matic 468_323)
  - Lannes Kenfield, Alfredo Trujillo, September 21, 1991; cuid29845 (Box 18, U-matic 468_246)
  - Steve Ben Israel, September 25, 1991; cuid29921 (Box 24, U-matic 468_324)
  - Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, October 16, 1991; cuid29922 (Box 24, U-matic 468_325)
  - Vegetarian - Pamela Teisler, October 16, 1991; cuid29923 (Box 24, U-matic 468_326)
  - Tuli Kupferberg, November 6, 1991; cuid29924 (Box 24, U-matic 468_327)
  - Cherry Vanilla, November 13, 1991; cuid29925 (Box 24, U-matic 468_328)
  - Mark Reilly, Tuli Kupferberg, November 27, 1991; cuid29914 (Box 23, U-matic 468_315)
  - Mark Riley, December 4, 1991; cuid29840 (Box 18, U-matic 468_241)
  - Jasmine, January 1, 1992; cuid29913 (Box 23, U-matic 468_314)
    The main guest is most likely Jasmine Vegas of the Fuxxons, but this is unconfirmed.
  - Judith Malina, Hanon Reznakov, January 15, 1992; cuid29901 (Box 22, U-matic 468_302)
  - Living Theatre - Judith Malina, Hanon Reznakov, January 22, 1992; cuid29902 (Box 22, U-matic 468_303)
  - Brian Benson, February 5, 1992; cuid29903 (Box 22, U-matic 468_304)
    This episode also features Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, and Answering Listener Calls.
  - Art D'Lugoff, February 12, 1992; cuid29904 (Box 22, U-matic 468_305)
  - Lori Rizzo, February 26, 1992; cuid29905 (Box 22, U-matic 468_306)
  - Ira Cohen, March 4, 1992; cuid29906 (Box 22, U-matic 468_307)
  - Jasmine, March 18, 1992; cuid29907 (Box 22, U-matic 468_308)
  - Joe Christ, March 25, 1992; cuid29908 (Box 23, U-matic 468_309)
  - Jasmine, April 8, 1992; cuid29909 (Box 23, U-matic 468_310)
  - VVAW, Brian Materese, Steve Geiger, April 15, 1992; cuid29910 (Box 23, U-matic 468_311)
  - Steve "Wildman" Brill, April 29, 1992; cuid29911 (Box 23, U-matic 468_312)
  - Steve Kohn from POWARS, May 13, 1992; cuid29912 (Box 23, U-matic 468_313)
  - Judith Malina, May 20, 1992; cuid29930 (Box 24, U-matic 468_333)
  - Country Joe McDonald, May 27, 1992; cuid29931 (Box 24, U-matic 468_334)
  - Jim Nev, Roger Babb, June 10, 1992; cuid29932 (Box 24, U-matic 468_335)
  - Radical Walking Tour with Bruce Kayton, Rainbow Room Stroke with Marianne DiSanto, June 10, 1992; cuid29933 (Box 24, U-matic 468_336)
  - Coe Perkinson, June 24, 1992; cuid29934 (Box 24, U-matic 468_337)
  - Mordehai Levy, Klan Kicker, July 1, 1992; cuid29935 (Box 25, U-matic 468_338)
  - Aron Kay, July 28, 1992; cuid29936 (Box 25, U-matic 468_339)
  - Joe Christ, August 4, 1992; cuid29847 (Box 18, U-matic 468_248)
    Duration: 31 minutes
  - Lori Rizzo, Jay Byrd, August 11, 1992; cuid29848 (Box 18, U-matic 468_249)
  - Kevin O'Neill, August 18, 1992; cuid29938 (Box 25, U-matic 468_341)
  - Jasmine, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, July 8, 1992; cuid29939 (Box 25, U-matic 468_342)
  - Cooking with mushrooms, Tuli Kupferberg, August 25, 1992; cuid29940 (Box 25, U-matic 468_343)
    Duration: 30 minutes; A note on the tape says "No Sound"; There is no sound for the first half of the episode.
  - Jasmine, September 1, 1992; cuid29886 (Box 21, U-matic 468_287)
    The main guest is most likely Jasmine Vegas of the Fuxxons.
  - Judith Malina, September 8, 1992; cuid29887 (Box 21, U-matic 468_288)
  - Charles Alkroft - The Broccoli from "Yesterdays Donuts", October 6, 1992; cuid29941 (Box 25, U-matic 468_344)
  - Cherry Vanilla, October 20, 1992; cuid29942 (Box 25, U-matic 468_345)
  - Terry Noel, John Peters, David Gochenour, October 27, 1992; cuid29943 (Box 25, U-matic 468_346)
  - Jim Neu and Bill Rice, November 10, 1992; cuid29944 (Box 25, U-matic 468_347)
  - Country Joe McDonald, November 24, 1992; cuid29857 (Box 19, U-matic 468_258)
  - Sal Solak and Brian Benson, December 1, 1992; cuid29858 (Box 19, U-matic 468_259)
  - Celso Loch, Brian Benson, The Psychedelic Solution with Jay, December 15, 1992; cuid29859 (Box 19, U-matic 468_260)
  - Lori Rizzo, December 18, 1992; cuid29915 (Box 23, U-matic 468_316)
    This episode also features Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Junot (?), and Gus Finkelstein.
    There are multiple dates on tape - 1/8/1992, Live 12/18/1991
  - Penny Arcade, December 22, 1992; cuid29860 (Box 19, U-matic 468_261)
  - Ira Cohen, January 19, 1993; cuid29862 (Box 19, U-matic 468_263)
    This episode also features Lannes Kenfield and Tuli Kupferberg.
  - Steve Ben Israel, January 26, 1993; cuid29861 (Box 19, U-matic 468_262)
  - American Dream, February 2, 1993; cuid29863 (Box 19, U-matic 468_264)
  - Joe Christ and excerpts from his film Crippled, Tuli Kupferberg, February 9, 1993; cuid29864 (Box 19, U-matic 468_265)
  - David Peel, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, February 23, 1993; cuid29849 (Box 18, U-matic 468_250)
  - David Peel, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, March 2, 1993; cuid29850 (Box 18, U-matic 468_251)
  - Jasmine, Lannes Kenfield, Tuli Kupferberg, Answering Phones, March 9, 1993; cuid29865 (Box 19, U-matic 468_266)
  - Save the Earth Woodstock, Tuli Kupferberg, March 16, 1993; cuid29866 (Box 20, U-matic 468_267)
  - George + George Washington, April 20, 1993; cuid29868 (Box 20, U-matic 468_269)
  - Kevin O'Neill, April 27, 1993; cuid29867 (Box 20, U-matic 468_268)